<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alloy on alloy</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/</link><description>Recent content in Alloy on alloy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>about</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/about/</guid><description>What is Alloy? It&amp;rsquo;s a little language for software modeling — essentially a logic for talking about structures and how they evolve — and an accompanying tool that can simulate and check models, covering billions of cases in seconds.
Why Alloy? Designing software is about devising structures and actions to transform one into another. In traditional software development, you keep these structures and actions in your head until you write code, or maybe jot them down in some vague sketches.</description></item><item><title>applications</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/applications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/applications/</guid><description>&lt;p>Alloy has been used as a design and analysis tool in a wide variety of applications
and projects in industry, research and teaching.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>book</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/book/</guid><description>&lt;p>Daniel Jackson&amp;rsquo;s book Software Abstractions offers a gentle and detailed introduction to modeling
and analysis in Alloy through a sequence of short examples.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Case Study Applications</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/citations/case-studies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/citations/case-studies/</guid><description>Selected papers that describe applications of Alloy:
Papers on Teaching with Alloy Teach foundational language principles Communications of the ACM Thomas Ball &amp;amp; Benjamin Zorn - 2015 Using Alloy in Introductory Courses of Formal Methods Structured Object-Oriented Formal Language and Method Shin Nakajima - 2014 - Springer Introducing Alloy in a Software Modelling Course Formal Methods in Computer Science J Noble, DJ Pearce&amp;hellip;, 2008.</description></item><item><title>courses</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/courses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/courses/</guid><description>&lt;p>Alloy is an ideal tool for teaching software modeling, since it offers a simple
relational modeling language and an accessible standalone tool that provides
novices with instant feedback.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>documentation</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/documentation/</guid><description>&lt;p>FAQ about the Alloy language and tools; reference guides; tutorials and quick introductions; &amp;hellip;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>download</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/download/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/download/</guid><description>Alloy is a self-contained executable, which includes the Kodkod model finder and a variety of SAT solvers, as well as the standard Alloy library and a collection of tutorial examples. The same jar file can be incorporated into other applications to use Alloy as an API, and includes the source code. See the release notes for details of new features. To execute, simply double-click on the jar file, or type java -jar org.</description></item><item><title>models</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/models/</guid><description>&lt;p>A collection of Alloy models to peruse&amp;hellip;&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>team</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/team/</guid><description>Alloy is an open source project maintained by a few key volunteers and a community of researchers. It was originally developed in the Software Design Group at MIT. The most recent version of Alloy is built on the MIT codebase; on the Kodkod engine, built by Emina Torlak in her thesis work at MIT, and now maintained by her as a free-standing model finder; and on a dynamic extension previously called Electrum, developed at ONERA and the University of Minho.</description></item><item><title>tools</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/resource/tools/</guid><description>&lt;p>Because it offers a powerful analysis engine for a very general logic, Alloy
and its model finding engine Kodkod have been used as backends for many more
specialized tools.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>