<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alloy</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/</link><description>Recent content on Alloy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/about/</guid><description>What is Alloy? It&amp;rsquo;s a little language for software modeling — essentially a logic for talking about structures and how they evolve — and an accompanying tool that can simulate and check models, covering billions of cases in seconds.
Why Alloy? Designing software is about devising structures and actions to transform one into another. In traditional software development, you keep these structures and actions in your head until you write code, or maybe jot them down in some vague sketches.</description></item><item><title>Applications</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/applications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/applications/</guid><description>Alloy is used in a wide variety of applications. The page provides links to some tools built on Alloy and Kodkod (Alloy’s model finding engine), and to lists of citations from Google Scholar of papers that discuss applications of Alloy.
Alloy Citations Google scholar A sample of over 1200 papers discussing Alloy case studies Selected papers describing applications of Alloy courses Courses using Alloy translations Papers on translating a dozen other languages into Alloy theses Theses about Alloy select tools built on alloy and kodkod Alloy* A general-purpose, higher-order, relational constraint solver aRby An embedding of Alloy in Ruby Forge A bounded verifier for Java code Squander Unified execution of imperative and declarative code Alloy4Eclipse Eclipse plugin for Alloy 4 DynAlloy An extension of Alloy with procedural actions TACO A bounded verifier for Java annotated with JML Equals Checker A tool for checking equals methods in Java Nitpick A counterexample generator for Isabelle/HOL Margrave A security policy analyzer for firewalls Secrecy Modeling Language (SML) A language for composing and validating security models.</description></item><item><title>Case Study Applications</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/citations/case-studies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/citations/case-studies/</guid><description>Selected papers that describe applications of Alloy:
Papers on Teaching with Alloy Teach foundational language principles Communications of the ACM Thomas Ball &amp;amp; Benjamin Zorn - 2015 Using Alloy in Introductory Courses of Formal Methods Structured Object-Oriented Formal Language and Method Shin Nakajima - 2014 - Springer Introducing Alloy in a Software Modelling Course Formal Methods in Computer Science J Noble, DJ Pearce&amp;hellip;, 2008.</description></item><item><title>Resource</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/fizzbang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/fizzbang/</guid><description>Fizz Bang Fizz Bang is a plugin for Alloy that delivers an electrical shock to the user when a counterexample is found.</description></item><item><title>Team</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/team/</guid><description>Alloy is a product of the Software Design Group at MIT.
alloy team members Daniel Jackson – Project director Aleksandar Milicevic – Lead developer &amp;amp; Master guru Emina Torlak – Developer, Kodkod engine Eunsuk Kang – General guru Joe Near – General guru former team members Major contributions to earlier versions of Alloy were made by: Felix Chang, Jonathan Edwards, Robert Seater, Derek Rayside, Greg Dennis, Ilya Shlyakhter, Mana Taghdiri, Mandana Vaziri, Sarfraz Khurshid, and Manu Sridharan.</description></item></channel></rss>