<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Essentials on alloy</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/</link><description>Recent content in Essentials on alloy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>about</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/about/</guid><description>What is Alloy? It&amp;rsquo;s a little language for software modeling — essentially a logic for talking about structures and how they evolve — and an accompanying tool that can simulate and check models, covering billions of cases in seconds.
Why Alloy? Designing software is about devising structures and actions to transform one into another. In traditional software development, you keep these structures and actions in your head until you write code, or maybe jot them down in some vague sketches.</description></item><item><title>download</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/download/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/download/</guid><description>Alloy is a self-contained executable, which includes the Kodkod model finder and a variety of SAT solvers, as well as the standard Alloy library and a collection of tutorial examples. The same jar file can be incorporated into other applications to use Alloy as an API, and includes the source code. See the release notes for details of new features. To execute, simply double-click on the jar file, or type java -jar org.</description></item><item><title>team</title><link>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hwayne.github.io/alloy-hugo-demo/main/team/</guid><description>Alloy is an open source project maintained by a few key volunteers and a community of researchers. It was originally developed in the Software Design Group at MIT. The most recent version of Alloy is built on the MIT codebase; on the Kodkod engine, built by Emina Torlak in her thesis work at MIT, and now maintained by her as a free-standing model finder; and on a dynamic extension previously called Electrum, developed at ONERA and the University of Minho.</description></item></channel></rss>