<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alloy on Alloytools Prototype</title><link>http://alloytools.org/page/</link><description>Recent content in Alloy on Alloytools Prototype</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://alloytools.org/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Alloy</title><link>http://alloytools.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://alloytools.org/about/</guid><description>Alloy is a language for describing structures and a tool for exploring them. It has been used in a wide range of applications from finding holes in security mechanisms to designing telephone switching networks.
An Alloy model is a collection of constraints that describes (implicitly) a set of structures, for example: all the possible security configurations of a web application, or all the possible topologies of a switching network. Alloy’s tool, the Alloy Analyzer, is a solver that takes the constraints of a model and finds structures that satisfy them.</description></item><item><title>Applications</title><link>http://alloytools.org/applications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://alloytools.org/applications/</guid><description>Alloy is used in a wide variety of applications. The page provides links to some tools built on Alloy and Kodkod (Alloy’s model finding engine), and to lists of citations from Google Scholar of papers that discuss applications of Alloy.
Alloy Citations Google scholar A sample of over 1200 papers discussing Alloy case studies Selected papers describing applications of Alloy courses Courses using Alloy translations Papers on translating a dozen other languages into Alloy theses Theses about Alloy select tools built on alloy and kodkod Alloy* A general-purpose, higher-order, relational constraint solver aRby An embedding of Alloy in Ruby Forge A bounded verifier for Java code Squander Unified execution of imperative and declarative code Alloy4Eclipse Eclipse plugin for Alloy 4 DynAlloy An extension of Alloy with procedural actions TACO A bounded verifier for Java annotated with JML Equals Checker A tool for checking equals methods in Java Nitpick A counterexample generator for Isabelle/HOL Margrave A security policy analyzer for firewalls Secrecy Modeling Language (SML) A language for composing and validating security models.</description></item></channel></rss>